// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following are CPU scheduling algorithms?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Priority scheduling",
      "Round Robin",
      "Shortest job first" ,
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A process which is copied from main memory to secondary memory on the basis of requirement is known as ",
    answer: "Demand paging",
    options: [
      "Paging",
      "Threads",
      "Segmentation",
      "Demand paging"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "FIFO scheduling is a type of:",
    answer: "Non-pre-emptive scheduling",
    options: [
      "Pre-emptive scheduling",
      "Deadline scheduling",
      "Non-pre-emptive scheduling",
      "Preventing deadlock"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A systematic procedure for moving the CPU to new process is known as-",
    answer: "Context switching",
    options: [
      "Synchornization",
      "Context switching",
      "Starvation",
      "Deadlock"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Thread is a",
    answer: "Light weight process",
    options: [
      "Light weight process",
      "Multi-process",
      "Heavy weight process",
      "I/O process"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Among the following CPU scheduling algorithms, which of these allocated the CPU first to the process that requests the CPU first?",
    answer: "FCFS",
    options: [
      "SJF",
      "FCFS",
      "Priority scheduling",
      "Preventing deadlock"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "For which of the following purposes in Bankerâ€™s algorithm is used?",
    answer: "Preventing deadlock",
    options: [
      "Solving deadlock",
      "Recover from deadlock",
      "Preventing deadlock",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The most optimal CPU scheduling algorithm is ________",
    answer: "Shortest job first",
    options: [
      "First come first serve",
      "Round robin ",
      "Shortest job first",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Which of the following are two types of atomic operations performed by semaphores?",
    answer: "wait,signal",
    options: [
      "wait,signal",
      "wait,stop",
      "signal,stop",
      "signal,hold"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "When can binding of instructions and data to memory addresses can be done?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Load time",
      "Compile time",
      "Execution time",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
];

